<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tianqi Zhao</title>
    <link>https://tianqizhao.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tianqi Zhao</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://tianqizhao.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://tianqizhao.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 01:21:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tianqizhao.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dareer: Brandeis Alumni&#39;s Career Path Database</title>
      <link>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/dareer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 01:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/dareer/</guid>
      <description>Why Dareer While I was working as an office assistant at Brandeis University, I was assigned to collect, clean, and visualize all CS alumni&amp;rsquo;s data, including their majors and their job history (companies and the corresponding employment duration). We spent six months just on collecting all the data and put it into a large Google Sheet file, and then we spent an entire semester on cleaning it.
We had a large team and without a clear documentation, different people had different habit of recording the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Go and Grab a Coffee while Keeping Your Vim Running on CLAC</title>
      <link>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/tmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 12:30:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/tmux/</guid>
      <description>While taking the Advanced Programming class, the thing that bothers me the most is not that we need to program using Vim in CLAC, a remote server, but every time when I leave for a cup of coffee, my laptop sleeps, and CLAC connection is automatically closed, so I have to type clac, cd cs3157/labN/part1, vim xxx.c again and again, which is really annoying.
Jae briefly mentioned a handy tool, called tmux, in listserv, and I found that is useful if you are a coffee person like me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://tianqizhao.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tianqizhao.com/about/</guid>
      <description>about</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
