<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Louis Zhao's Portfolio</title><link>https://tianqizhao.com/categories/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Louis Zhao's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tianqizhao.com/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Interactive Encyclopedia Using GPT-3</title><link>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/interactive-encyclopedia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:13:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/interactive-encyclopedia/</guid><description>Customer Analysis Who would use it? Young children from elementary school
What essential need does it address? Young children are always curious about everything new in life and always ask a chain of questions. Parents/teachers might not be able to answer every question as soon as they come up.
What is the essential solution to address that need? When kids enter question, the &amp;ldquo;encyclopedia&amp;rdquo; can find answer and reply interactively.</description></item><item><title>Columbia Ambient Sound</title><link>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/columbia-ambient-sound/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 17:13:44 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/columbia-ambient-sound/</guid><description>Target Users Columbia students who like to have a customized relaxing/peaceful/focused environment using ambient sounds while they are busy doing things, and live off-campus but still want to connect with the university in some ways.
What Problems Are We Solving This ambient sound skill can help people relax, reduce stress and anxiety, improve focus and productivity, and create a more soothing environment based on particular use cases. It can also help mask distracting noises that may be present in the background.</description></item><item><title>Paws and Tails Built in Ruby on Rails</title><link>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/paws-and-tails-rails/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 16:42:10 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/paws-and-tails-rails/</guid><description>Story As a pet lover, I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting a Ragdoll for so long. During my search for a cat, I figured out that although there are plenty of websites connecting shelters with petfinders, there isn&amp;rsquo;t a single successful platform connecting breeders with petlovers.
Right now, if you want to find a breeder, you have to go online and search for &amp;ldquo;best Ragdoll breeders in New York City&amp;rdquo;. This will lead you to watch tons of bad-designed websites, send countless emails, do many interviews, pay deposit fees, and finally - you have to wait for six months for the litter.</description></item><item><title>CADO: An Online Daycare Platform Designed for Kids</title><link>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/cado/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 01:27:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/cado/</guid><description>Story Working from home as a mother can feel like paradise. But, you have back-to-back meetings, an upcoming product release, and presentations to upper management with your children crying and running around. How do you concentrate?
CADO aims to provide an online daycare to keep your children busy and distracted on our cloud meeting platform designed for kids. You won’t need to worry about balancing work and your children’s education because through interactive activities, we teach them life skills, language courses, and simple math - you choose it!</description></item><item><title>Brandeis Career: Brandeis Alumni's Career Path Database</title><link>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/brandeis-career/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 01:21:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://tianqizhao.com/posts/brandeis-career/</guid><description>Why Brandeis Career While I was working as an office assistant at Brandeis University, I was assigned to collect, clean, and visualize all CS alumni&amp;rsquo;s data, including their majors and their job history (companies and the corresponding employment duration). We spent six months just on collecting all the data and put it into a large Google Sheet file, and then we spent an entire semester on cleaning it.
We had a large team and without a clear documentation, different people had different habit of recording the data.</description></item></channel></rss>